Guide to the Silicon Valley Ephemera Collection, 1976- M0443
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Publications, Series 1
  - National Semiconductor Corp., Subseries 1.16
    - National Semiconductor Corp. Memory databook. -- Santa Clara, Calif.: National Semiconductor, 1978; Accession no. 2003-322; 1 v. (Box 32, Volume 8)
    - National Semiconductor Corp. MOS/LSI. -- Santa Clara, Calif.: National Semiconductor, 1978; Accession no. 2003-322; 1 v. (Box 32, Volume 9)
    - National Semiconductor Corp. Pressure transducer handbook. -- Santa Clara, Calif.: National Semiconductor, 1978; Accession no. 2003-322; 1 v. (Box 32, Volume 10)
    - National Semiconductor Corp. Special function data book. -- Santa Clara, Calif.: National Semiconductor, 1976; Accession no. 2003-322; 1 v. (Box 32, Volume 11)
    - National Semiconductor Corp. Transistors small signal field effect power. -- Santa Clara, Calif.: National Semiconductor, 1973; Accession no. 2003-322; 1 v. (Box 32, Volume 12)
  - Next Corp., Subseries 1.17
    - Next Corporation. Documentation, 1991; Accession no. 2003-335 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      Donated by Prof. Nils Nilsson.
      Release notes -- Network and system administration -- Applications -- User's reference -- Setup and tutorials.
  - Pasternak Enterprises, Subseries 1.18
    - Pasternak Enterprises. Catalog, undated; Accession no. 2003-322 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Philco, Subseries 1.19
    - Philco. Catalog, 1985; Accession no. 2003-322 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Plessey Semiconductors, Subseries 1.20
    - Plessey Semiconductors. Product brochure, undated; Accession no. 2003-322 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - RS Electronic Corp., Subseries 1.21
    - RS Electronic Corp. Product brochure, undated; Accession no. 2003-322 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Schadow ITT, Subseries 1.22
    - Schadow ITT. Catalog, undated; Accession no. 2003-322 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Sierra Electronic Corp., Subseries 1.23
    - Sierra Electronic Corp. Brochure, 1955; Accession no. 2003-322; 1 v. (cy. 1) (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Sierra Electronic Corp. Brochure, 1955; Accession no. 2003-322; 1 v. (cy. 2) (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Sierra Electronic Corp. Transistor test, model 219B: instructions and parts breakdown, circa 1955; Accession no. 2003-322 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Sierra Systems, Inc., Subseries 1.24
    - Sierra Systems, Inc. Product brochures, undated; Accession no. 2003-322 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Signetics, Subseries 1.25
    - Signetics analog: applications manual, 1979 Jan; Accession no. 2003-322 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Signetics analog: data manual, 1979 Jan; Accession no. 2003-322 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Signetics logic - TTL: data manual, 1978 May; Accession no. 2003-322 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Signetics. Product brochures and specifications, 1970; Accession no. 2003-322 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Siliconix, Inc., Subseries 1.26
    - Siliconix, Inc. Analog switches and their applications, 1976; 1 v. (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Siliconix, Inc. Analog switch & IC product data book, 1982 Jan; Accession no. 2003-322; 1 v. (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Siliconix, Inc. Field-effect transistors, 1974; Accession no. 2003-322 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Siliconix, Inc. MOSpower design catalog, 1983 Jan; Accession no. 2003-322 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Siliconix, Inc. Product brochure, 1970; Accession no. 2003-322 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Silicon State Technology. Product brochure, 1971; Accession no. 2003-322 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Tektronix, Inc., Subseries 1.27
    - Tektronix, Inc. Promotional flyer, circa 1990; 1 item (Box 25, Folder 15)
      Promotional flyer for the Tektronix Phaser 200 color printer.
    - Tektronix, Inc. 1401 spectrum analyzer module: instruction manual, 1970; 1 v. (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Tektronix, Inc. Type 1L20 spectrum analyzer module: instruction manual, 1970; 1 v. (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Tektronix, Inc. Type 515, 551A oscilloscopes: instruction manual, 1970; 1 v. (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Watkins - Johnson Co., Subseries 1.28
    - Watkins - Johnson Co. Key personnel and current projects, 1961 Sep; 1 v. (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Watkins - Johnson Co. brochures, circa 1961 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous retailers, Subseries 1.29
    - Miscellaneous retailers. brochures, undated (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Accession 2016-283: Price/Configuration guides
    - HP, DataPro, Conam and TRW price and configuration guides, 1969-1995 (Box 37-50)
- Software packages and manuals, Series 2
  Access
  The Media materials require at least two weeks advance notice to use in order to allow staff time to have use copies made from the original items.
  - Manuals, Subseries 2.1
    - Intuit. Quicken user manual, ver. 3, for IBM and PC compatibles. -- Palo Alto, Calif.: Intuit, 1989; 1 v. (Box 1, Volume 1)
    - Leading Edge Hardware Products, Inc. Guide to Basic, Version 3.20, for the Model "D". -- Canton, Mass.: Leading Edge Hardware Products, Inc., 1987; 1 item. (Box 1, Volume 2)
    - Leading Edge Hardware Products, Inc. Ms-Dos Reference manual, Version 3.20, for the Model "D". -- Canton, Mass.: Leading Edge Hardware Products, Inc., 1987; 1 item. (Box 1, Volume 3)
    - Leading Edge Hardware Products, Inc. Ms-Dos User's guide, Version 3.20, for the Model "D". -- Canton, Mass.: Leading Edge Hardware Products, Inc., 1987; 1 item. (Box 1, Volume 4)
    - MicroPro International Corp. WordStar Professional, release 5, 1988; 1 v. (Box 1, Volume 5)
    - MicroPro International Corp. WordStar Professional, release 5: pocket Wordstar, 1988; 1 v. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Microsoft Corporation. Microsoft MS-DOS Operating System version 5.0 User's guide and reference, 1991; 1 v. (Box 1, Volume 6)
    - Microsoft Corporation. Microsoft Word pocket guide for Microsoft Windows and OS/2 presentation manager, 1989 - 1990; 1 v. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Software Toolworks. LISP/80, ver. 1.0 [user's manual], 1981; 1 v. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Software packages, Subseries 2.2
    - Intuit. Quicken, ver. 2.0 for Windows [kit], 1992; 2 computer diskettes: 5.25 in. + 1 computer diskette: 3.5 in. + 1 v. (Box 2)
    - Intuit. Quicken, ver. 6.0 for DOS [kit], 1992; 3 computer diskettes: 5.25 in. + 1 v. (Box 2)
    - MicroPro International Corp. WordStar [kit], 1983; 2 computer diskettes [note: missing]: 5.25 in. + 1 v. (Box 2)
    - MicroPro International Corp. WordStar Professional, release 5 [kit], 1988; 11 computer diskettes: 5.25 in. + 5 v. (Box 3)
    - NextStep Academic Bundle: object-oriented software, release 3.2 for Intel 486 & Pentium processors [kit], 1993; 3 CD-ROM disks + 1 computer diskette: 3.5 in. + 6 v. (Box 4)
    - SpryInternet in a box, Windows version, 1995; 1 item (Box 5)
    - Sun Moon Star personal computer system manual [kit], 1988; 2 computer diskettes: 5.25 in. + 2 v. (Box 6)
    - Lotus Improve for the NeXT computer [kit], 1991; Accession no. 2003-335; 2 computer diskettes: 5.25 in. + 2 v. (Box 7)
    - NextStep Academic Bundle: object-oriented software, release 3.3 for Intel 486 & Pentium processors [kit], 1994; Accession no. 2003-335; 3 CD-ROM disks + 1 computer diskette: 3.5 in. + 6 v. (Box 7)
    - Mathematica for NeXT computers, version 2.0 [kit], 1991; Accession no. 2003-335; 2 computer diskettes: 5.25 in. + 8 enclosures. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - NeXT software release, release 2.1, 1991; Accession no. 2003-335; 1 computer diskette: 5.25 in. (Box 8)
    - Allegro CL Common LISP, release 3.1 [kit]. -- [S.l.]: Franz Inc., 1991; Accession no. 2003-335; 1 kit: unopened. NeXT 2.0 operating system (Box 8)
    - Sybase [kit]. -- [S.l.]: Sybase Inc., 1991; Accession no. 2003-335; 1 kit: unopened. NeXT 2.0 operating system (Box 8)
  - Electronic media, Subseries 2.3
    - Adobe Systems. Adobe Solutions & Product Sampler, Issue no. 3, 1998; 1 computer optical disk (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Adobe Systems. Adobe Solutions & Product Sampler, Issue no. 6, 1998; 2 computer optical disks (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Intel Corp. Intel OverDrive processer application demo, 1993; 1 computer diskette: 3.5 in. IBM format (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Microsoft Corp. Microsoft Window 95 interactive demo & sampler, 1995; 1 computer optical disk (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Rogers ranting: for distribution, undated; Accession no. 2003-335; 1 computer diskette; 3.5 in. MacIntosh format (cy. 1) (Box 8)
    - Rogers ranting: for distribution, undated; Accession no. 2003-335; 1 computer diskette; 3.5 in. MacIntosh format (cy. 2) (Box 8)
    - Memex, undated; Accession no. 2003-335; 1 computer diskette; 3.5 in. (Box 8)
- Audiovisual materials, Series 3
  - Silicon Graphics Computer Systems. Rediscover engineering. -- (Superworkstation demonstration), circa 1987; 1 video cassette (Flat-box 1)
  - Mann, Charles Kellogg, 1934, ed. Professionals sharing knowledge. -- (The Powersharing People, Computers and You series / Charles K. Mann, ed.), 1986; 1 v. + 32 sound cassettes (Box 2)
    Wozniak, Steve, 1950-; Graetz, Martin; Gottheil, Bill; Gross, Bill; Green, Adam; Hawkins, Trip; Gross, Larry P.; Klatt, D.H. (Dennis H.); Kahn, Philippe; Kotok, Alan; Komoski, P. Kenneth; Kurzweil, Ray; Kurland, D. Midian; McKenna, Regis; Launey, Reuel O.; Osborne, Adam; O'Brien, Peggy; Papert, Seymour; Bricklin, Dan; Pariseau, Robert; Chowaniec, Adam; Raskin, Jef; Bosworth, Adam; Rattigan, Thomas; Bowman, William; Rosen, Benjamin; Abrams, Rick; Selfridge, Oliver; Anderson, Howard; Shapiro, Neil L.; Snyder, Tom; Frankston, Robert; Solomon, Les; Garnett, Terrence; Techner, Walt; Forester, Jeanne Marie; Tramiel, Leonard; Foskett, A.C. (Antony Charles); Vanginderen, Joseph; Driscoll, Alexis; Vogeli, Bruce R. (Bruce Ramon); Dyson, Esther; Winner, Alice-Anne; Cohen, Bruce I. (Bruce Ira); Dow, Stephen; Yocam, Del
- Ephemera
  - Pets.com sock puppet, 1999 (Carton Series 4 Carton 1)